<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zhongtao&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>https://dozz-m.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zhongtao&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dozz-m.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://dozz-m.github.io/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dozz-m.github.io/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m currently 🎓 Undergraduate at ShanghaiTech University, majoring in Electronic Information Engineering. 🎯Aim at bringing reliable and helpful humanoid into daily life. 🌱 Interested in control &amp;amp; design of bipedal robot and animatronic robotic face. Experience Motor and Motion-Control Lab (8.2023–Present) Mentor: Prof. Chen Jiahao Mechanical Design and Control for quasi-direct-drive bipedal robot.. Nonlinear B-controller: design and optimization for dynamical gain controller. Power System Protection &amp;amp; Automation Laboratory(6.2022-8.2023) Mentor: Prof. Liu Yu Using single-ended measurement to locate faults on the mixed-transmission line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accurate Single-Ended Fault Location for Cable-OHL Hybrid Transmission Lines</title>
      <link>https://dozz-m.github.io/posts/projects/accurate-single-ended-fault-location-for-cable-ohl-hybrid-transmission-lines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dozz-m.github.io/posts/projects/accurate-single-ended-fault-location-for-cable-ohl-hybrid-transmission-lines/</guid>
      <description>Motivation Transmission lines consist of overhead lines (OHLs) and underground cables, as underground cables, are what we called Hybrid Transmission Lines, who are widely used adopted connecting sources (e.g. offshore wind turbines) or consumers at sea.
Single-ended methods, which are more attractive to field engineers, need only one end of measurement and need no expensive synchronized and communication between two ends via satellites. However, existing methods fail to fully consider distributed line parameters, bringing errors to the fault location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>B-Control: parameter line based dynamic gain controller</title>
      <link>https://dozz-m.github.io/posts/projects/b-controller_dynamic_gain_controller/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dozz-m.github.io/posts/projects/b-controller_dynamic_gain_controller/</guid>
      <description>Motivation A controller, essentially a mapping from current known information to next time output, utilizes system state be it to observer or measured and user input to make decisions. However, relying solely on a constant gain for this mapping seems to be not optimal. For example, a big control gain means small steady state error and fast responses to control system, but has bigger overshoot and make actuator easier to saturation, while small gain implies big steady state error, slow response, even though it fix problem of saturation and overshoot.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
